Hoang Vy Duong

Software Engineer

PROFILE

Startup lover, with experience in building, designing and developing from scratch or renewing projects. Like to grow team, help each other to grow together, and contribute to the company's growth.

hoangvypfiev@gmail.com (+84) 943723427 12-07-1995 Viet Nam

EXPERIENCE

PrimeData

Senior Software Engineer

April 2022 - Now, Ho Chi Minh

PrimeData is a CDP solution to empower the creativity of Marketers and Digitalists in Customers analytics 360 and Omni-channel marketing automation.

Refactor the engagement tool: redefine project structure, add unit test, integrate new channels (Facebook, SMS), and increase the overall performance of message-delivering to be able to serve 1 million messages per minute (test without channel-plugins).

Build team culture, collaborate with other teams.

Build data pipeline to collect data from multiple customers's sources to data warehouse.

Help to support customers for integrating with CDP platform.

Using: MicroService, Golang, SQL, Kafka, Postgres, K8s.

Tiki - DoriDori

Senior Software Engineer

May 2021 - April 2022, Ho Chi Minh

A part of DoriDori project: a social recommerce startup belongs to Tiki with the goal of hitting the second-hand market.

The very-first member of the project, help to research markets and suggest ideas for final business model.

Design most of the project's features include: Authorization, Order Management, Product Management, Newsfeed, Social Interaction, Logistic Integration, SAP Integration.

Develop CI process.

Build observable tools by Prometheus, Jaeger, Grafana.

Lead 3-member team, mentor fresher level to middle level by one year.

Using: MicroService, Golang, Postgres, Mongo, Kafka, K8s.

Zalopay

Software Engineer

June 2019 - May 2021, Ho Chi Minh

Design and implement logic, CI, log and monitor notification service with low latency (<=50ms) able to support 10000 concurrent requests.

Design and implement a part of ekyc service for verifying Zalopay user.

Using: Golang, Kafka, Grpc, Redis, MySQL, Consul, Nomad, GitlabCl, Prometheus, Loki.

Axon Active

Web Developer

July 2017 - June 2019, Da Nang

Crawl and prepare data for real-time public transportation tracking using Python, PostgreSQL.

Build RESTful services for supporting APIs by Spring Boot, Play Framework, RabbitMQ, Redis.

Develope dashboard admin for viewing the analytics by ReactJs.

Axon Active

Intern Web Developer

May 2017 - July 2017, Da Nang

EDUCATION

Information Technology

Da Nang University of Science Technology

2018, Da Nang

Languages

English